dateolicious.com 2012-05-11

# Privacy | Dateolicious

Edit Profile New Users My City Search User My Matches Top Rated |  |  |  |  |  Dating Sites |  Quick Dates |  Ice Breaker |  Chat! | 

##  Privacy Policy Agreement 

In an effort to secure your privacy when using Dateolicious.com we have established a policy to explain to you what is collected and used whenever you use our site. We recognize the importance of one’s privacy, especially on the internet. Therefore, we have been very vigilant in making sure your information, is yours and yours alone. That being said... We reserve the right to update, amend, and delete any part of this policy agreement at any time and for any reason with or without your notice to such changes. So let’s begin, shall we?   

##  Instances in which Dateolicious.com may share your personal information 

##  Instances in which Dateolicious.com may share your personal information 

##  Advertisement and Links 

##  Information we collect and how it is and may be used 

##  Person under the age of 18 

Dateolicious.com is not indented for individuals under the age of 18. If you are currently under the age of 18 and have signed up for our service, please discontinue use of the site immediately. In the event, personally Identifiable information is collected from an individual under the age of 18; all data stored for that individual will be promptly and thoroughly deleted.   

Your Dateolicious.com account is password protected for your privacy, safety and security. Although, we here at Dateolicious.com have made every effort from a technical standpoint to secure your information, the full burden and responsibility rest on your for securing your information. One way you can do so is to log off a shared computer once you are finish using it and by not sharing your login username and password credentials with anyone. If you feel that your account has been compromise please contact us immediately. 

We may, but are not obligated to, disclose your information if required to do so by law. This may include, but is not limited to, subpoenas, court orders, or any other legal process. 

Dateolicioius.com uses third party companies, such as Google, to serve ads on the site. These companies do not collect personally identifiable information (such as name, email address, or telephone number) about your interaction with the site. Instead what is collected and aggregated, is from non-personally identifiable information (age, zip code, location, etc), in order to target specific advertisement to you. Dateolicious.com is not responsible for and do not have control over which, what, how cookies are saved on your computer from theses third party ad servers. If you would like to learn more about Google’s privacy policy, you can do so here. Additionally, Dateolicious.com host links to other third party sites. When you, the user, clicks on the link, you will be sent to specific website the link is named after. No information is collected from you, whatsoever, when the link is clicked.   

As a new user to our website, you have freely provided us with information that relates to who you are, where you are, and how old you are just to name a few. Some additional user submitted information may include photographs, email address, zip codes, and sexual orientation. We also collect non-personally identifiable information such as, your IP address, browser type, and when you last visited the site. The information both personally identifiable and non-personally identifiable are not shared with anyone except required to do so by law.   

Last Updated: 03/22/2010
